Allen Veloria

+63 948-270-0806 | allenveloria14@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/allenveloria Binangonan Rizal

SYSTEM ANALYST - APPLICATION SUPPORT

System Analyst with over 4 years of experience and a strong background in Oracle SQL, and PL/SQL. Closed 1000+ tickets while working as an Application Support and involved in the deployment of several enhancements while working as an Oracle developer. One of the Technical leads for L2 Support that supports Core System Applications. Can work on a cross-functional team to meet SLAs, OKRs, and Targets.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Allianz PNB Life Nov 2022 - Present

System Analyst - Application Support (Technical Lead) | Apr 2024 - Present

- Technical Lead for L2 Application Support Team
- Provided Code reviews, Investigations, Knowledge Transfers, and Technical Analysis for the L2 Support Team

Application Support Analyst (Technical Lead) | Nov 2022 - Apr 2024

- Guided the L2 Manage Services in providing support by reviewing codes, answering inquiries, performing knowledge transfers, investigations, etc. for Allianz Core Systems.
- Created detailed Scripts and Documentation for L2 Manage Services for fixing Production-related issues.
- Provided support to business users if needed for urgent production requests/incidents.
- Created automated scripts for extraction of User's needed information.
- Created / Updated the processes of L2 Manage Support in handling user requests.
- Became the SME (Subject Matter Expert) for the Compensation-related topics or concerns.
- Reviewed and Approved data change/fix requests for movement to test and production environment.
- Conducted knowledge transfer sessions to L2 Manage Services about Core System processes and Business Rules.

Computer Professionals Inc.

Aug 2019 - Nov 2022

Oracle Developer | May 2022 - Nov 2022

- Deployed in Allianz PNB Life as an Oracle Developer for the Products & Partnership development team.
- Contributed to System enhancements and development of new products and funds.
- Supported the team lead for the documentation of changes for the deployment to production.
- Provided knowledge transfer sessions for the newly deployed changes for funds/plans.
- Involved in the deployment to the production of 3 Allianz funds/plans.

Application Support Analyst | Feb 2020 - May 2022

- Deployed in Allianz PNB Life as an Application Support for Allianz Core Systems.
- Focused on maintaining the correct production data by doing data fixes, incident investigations, data extractions, supporting business user concerns, and meeting SLAs and targets.
- Became the main support for the Policy contract, Compensation, and Distribution concerns and issues.
- Provided knowledge transfer sessions to new hires of the team.
- Closed 1000+ tickets worth of data fixes, incidents, and data extractions.

Junior Oracle Developer | Sep 2019 - Feb 2020

- Deployed in CPI Special Projects team as an Oracle Developer.
- Focused on creating automated reports that used the database data for the newly developed system.
- Created Oracle procedures, functions, and reports that will be called and used by the system.

Developer Trainee | Aug 2019 - Sep 2019

- Gained training and Certification for the following:
 - Java Programming
 - SQL and PLSQL
 - Jasper iReport

TECHNICAL SKILL

- SQL
- PL/SQL
- Jasper iReports
- Oracle Forms and Reports
- ServiceNow

- Web Development (Basic)
- Python (Basic)
- Scrum Framework
- JIRA
- Github

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig